{
    "id": "4bed2d7966eb4d80bbd3c435d6d95bf6",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise For Beginners",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Little Jack Horner sat ……………….. a corner.",
            "description": "We use 'in' to indicate position in a three-dimensional space. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "242d571b65ac486b841621cf88aea217"
        },
        {
            "question": "The lion and the unicorn fought …………………. the crown.",
            "description": "They didn't fight with the crown. That means they didn't use the crown as a weapon. They fought because they both wanted the crown. ",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7539ede61c9544b1a83888519fe4a30c"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. the street, the Piper stepped.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In",
                "Into",
                "On"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4840e0e5f1f2414e9a4ada8cc8105264"
        },
        {
            "question": "She sat ………………… the fire, and told me a tale.",
            "description": "By can mean 'near'. Besides means 'in addition'.",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "besides"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b5cc7ddec5474116b40d6ec0a11b651d"
        },
        {
            "question": "They all ran ………………….. the farmer’s wife, who cut off their tails with a carving knife.",
            "description": "To run after somebody is to pursue them.",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "for",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "549d167f954a4d219c6ccf677ca5b22c"
        },
        {
            "question": "They rise ………………….. the morning lark, and labor till almost dark.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "abf998ab675b410baedabf7a069f5f84"
        },
        {
            "question": "I bring fresh showers ..................... the thirsting flowers from the seas and the streams.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d0af79ed5ed64c5d8e59fdfde52e1782"
        },
        {
            "question": "She laid her arms ………………….. her breast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "103ef3bd1ac84d269ac137558140f2fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "He swore ………………… the Nine Gods.",
            "description": "We swear by something.",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a520d5bf09e74f5c90e6a5e2232ed25f"
        },
        {
            "question": "We go away ............................ three weeks every summer.",
            "description": "For indicates duration since shows the starting point.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "19ca67b269db4be6a354c1f6d4013b72"
        },
        {
            "question": "Come and see us ............................ Christmas day.",
            "description": "We use on to talk about one day of the holiday.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1058cf202f4e4c69b703aa7c484eeada"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will phone you ...................... 30",
            "description": "We use 'at' with clock times.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "faa474c7e3d44409b80b1b1b8878ba94"
        }
    ]
}